Guide to the Barry Gifford Papers M0927
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Manuscripts
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1978 [3 of 3], undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    TMs, 28 pp.
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1978 [1 of 2], undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1978 [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    TMs, 32 pp.
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1978 [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    TMs, pp. 1-35
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1978 [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    TMs, pp. 36-66
  - Beautiful Phantoms: Poems 1968-1980; Mock-Up, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Before Cathay, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    TMsS, 50 pp.
  - A Boy's Novel [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    TMs, 45 pp.
  - A Boy's Novel [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    TMs, 43 pp.
  - A Boy's Novel [1 of 4], undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - A Boy's Novel [2 of 4], undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - A Boy's Novel [3 of 4], undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    TMs, 11 pp.
  - A Boy's Novel [4 of 4], undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    TMs, 46 pp.
  - A Boy's Novel, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    TMs, 28 pp; 1 ALS
  - The Boy You Have Always Loved: Poems 1967-1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    TMs, 57 pp.
  - Chinese Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Chinese Notes: original manuscript, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Consuelo's Kiss [1 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Consuelo's Kiss [2 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Consuelo's Kiss [3 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    AMs, 59 pp.
  - Coyote Tantras [1 of 22], undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    TMs (photocopy), 12 pp.
  - Coyote Tantras [2 of 22], undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Coyote Tantras [3 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Coyote Tantras [4 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Coyote Tantras [5 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Coyote Tantras [6 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    TMs, 13 pp.
  - Coyote Tantras [7 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Coyote Tantras [8 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Coyote Tantras [9 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Coyote Tantras [10 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Coyote Tantras [11 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Coyote Tantras [12 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Coyote Tantras [13 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Coyote Tantras [14 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Coyote Tantras [15 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    TMs, 25 pp.; 1 TLS (from Michael Anania)
  - Coyote Tantras [16 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Coyote Tantras [17 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Coyote Tantras [18 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Coyote Tantras [19 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Coyote Tantras [20 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Coyote Tantras [21 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Coyote Tantras [22 of 22], undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    TMs, 35 pp.
  - Coyote Tantras and Persimmons: Books I-IV [1 of 5], undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Coyote Tantras and Persimmons: Books I-IV [2 of 5], undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Coyote Tantras and Persimmons: Books I-IV [3 of 5], undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Coyote Tantras and Persimmons: Books I-IV [4 of 5], undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Coyote Tantras and Persimmons: Books I-IV [5 of 5], undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    TMs, 15 pp.
  - The Daring Young Man on the Flying Trapeze: A Portrait of William Saroyan; treatment, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - The Daring Young Man on the Flying Trapeze: A Portrait of William Saroyan, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    AMs, 5 pp.
  - The Daring Young Man on the Flying Trapeze: A Portrait of William Saroyan: "Hamish Good", undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    TMs, 3 pp.
  - The Daring Young Man on the Flying Trapeze: A Portrait of William Saroyan: "Hamish Good", undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    AMs, 3 pp.
  - The Daring Young Man on the Flying Trapeze: A Portrait of William Saroyan: Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    1 TLsS, 2 pp.
  - A Day at the Races (Atlantic Monthly Press, 1988): original typescript [1 of 5], circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    front matter. TMs, 10 pp.; 1 TLS
  - A Day at the Races (Atlantic Monthly Press, 1988): original typescript [2 of 5], circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    TMs, pp. 3A -50
  - A Day at the Races (Atlantic Monthly Press, 1988): original typescript [3 of 5], circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    TMs, pp. 51 -100
  - A Day at the Races (Atlantic Monthly Press, 1988): original typescript [4 of 5], circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    TMs, pp. 101 -150
  - A Day at the Races (Atlantic Monthly Press, 1988): original typescript [5 of 5], circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    TMs, pp. 151 -207
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interview with Floyd Prospero, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    TMs, ~ 50 pp.
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [1 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    TMs, ~ 25 pp.
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [2 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [3 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [4 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [5 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interviews [6 of 6], undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - A Day at the Races: typescript of interview with Bill Reed, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    TMs, 8 pp.
  - A Day at the Races: racetrack drawings, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - A Day at the Races: research materials [Sports Illustrated.--Vol. 66, no. 8], 1987 Feb 23 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: original manuscript [1 of 4], undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: original manuscript [2 of 4], undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: original manuscript [3 of 4], undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: original manuscript [4 of 4], undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    TMs, 64 pp.
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: research materials and notes [1 of 3], circa 1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: research materials and notes [2 of 3], circa 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: research materials and notes [3 of 3], circa 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: research materials [Los Angeles Daily Racing Form.--Vol. 60, no. 177], 1987 June 26 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [1 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [2 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [3 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [4 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [5 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [6 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [7 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [8 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [9 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [10 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [11 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [12 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [13 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [14 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [15 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [16 of 27], undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [17 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [18 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [19 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [20 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [21 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [22 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [23 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [24 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [25 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [26 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - A Day at the Races: The Education of a Racetracker: transcript of interviews [27 of 27], undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: original manuscript [1 of 2], 1987 Nov 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    TMs, 50 pp.; 1 ANS
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: original manuscript [2 of 2], 1987 Nov 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    TMs, 55 pp.
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [1 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 14)
    front matter: TMs, 15 pp.
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [2 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 15)
    TMs, pp. 1 -50
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [3 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [4 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [5 of 6] (Box 14, Folder 18)
    TMs, pp. 151 -200
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films (Grove Press, 1988): original manuscript [6 of 6] (Box 15, Folder 1)
    TMs, pp. 200 -246
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films [1 of 3], circa 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films [2 of 3], circa 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films [3 of 3], circa 1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: publication announcements from Grove Press [2 copies], 1988 Spring (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: correspondence, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: color slide of cover art, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: reviews and publicity, circa 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Devil Thumbs a Ride & other unforgettable films: uncut wrapper for paperbound edition, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The Duke of Earls Court [from "Francis goes to the seashore"]: original typescript, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Francis goes to the seashore: the second pillow book of Francis Reeves [1 of 3], undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Francis goes to the seashore: the second pillow book of Francis Reeves [2 of 3], undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Francis goes to the seashore: the second pillow book of Francis Reeves [3 of 3], undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    TMs, 47 pp.
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [1 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    TMs, 22 pp.
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [2 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [3 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [4 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [5 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [6 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [7 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    TMs, 18 pp.
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [8 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [9 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [10 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [11 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [12 of 13], undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    TMs, 16 pp.
  - Ghosts no horse can carry [13 of 13], undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    TMs, 26 pp.
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [1 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [2 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [3 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [4 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [5 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [6 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [7 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry and Three Romances [8 of 8], undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [1 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 10)
    TMs, 50 pp.; 1 postcard
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [2 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [3 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [4 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [5 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [6 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: Collected Poems, 1967 - 1987: typescript of manuscript [7 of 7], 1988 Nov (Box 16, Folder 16)
    TMs, 31 pp.
  - Ghosts No Horse Can Carry: uncorrected galley proof, 1989 Jan 16 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    TMs, 306 pp.; ANS
  - The Giants are going to win the pennant [broadside], undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Giotto's Circle [1 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    TMsS, 55 pp.
  - Giotto's Circle [2 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    TMsS, 37 pp.
  - Giotto's Circle and other poems, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    TMs, 51 pp.
  - Giotto's Circle, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Giotto's Circle, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    TMs, 72 pp.
  - The Godless world of Jim Thompson, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    TMs with holographic notes, 5 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [1 of 5], undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    AMs, 6 pp.; TMs, 50 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [2 of 5], undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - A Good Man to Know [3 of 5], undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - A Good Man to Know [4 of 5], undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - A Good Man to Know [5 of 5], undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    TMs, 36 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know: notes file, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - A Good Man to Know: notes file, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - A Good Man to Know: research materials, 1983 June 8 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - A Good Man to Know: research materials, circa 1984 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - A Good Man to Know: research materials, 1984 Jul-Aug (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - A Good Man to Know [1 of 4], undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 1 -vi, 1 -50 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [2 of 4], undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 51 -100 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [3 of 4], undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 101 -150 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [4 of 4], undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 151 -205 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know: a Semi-Documentary Fictional Memoir (revised) [1 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - A Good Man to Know: a Semi-Documentary Fictional Memoir (revised) [2 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - A Good Man to Know: a Semi-Documentary Fictional Memoir (revised) [3 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - A Good Man to Know: a Semi-Documentary Fictional Memoir (revised) [4 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - A Good Man to Know: a Semi-Documentary Fictional Memoir (revised) [5 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - A Good Man to Know: original manuscript and revised version [1 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - A Good Man to Know: original manuscript and revised version [2 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - A Good Man to Know: original manuscript and revised version [3 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - A Good Man to Know: original manuscript and revised version [4 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - A Good Man to Know: original manuscript and revised version [5 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    TMs, 37 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [1 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    TMsS, 49 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [2 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - A Good Man to Know [3 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    TMsS, 48 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know [4 of 5], undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - A Good Man to Know [5 of 5], undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    TMsS, 35 pp.
  - A Good Man to Know: "The favorite", undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    TMs, 5 pp.; ANS
  - A Good Man to Know: "The favorite", undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Horse hauling out of Hokkaido forest; Lives of the French Impressionist painters; Kerouac's Town; and St. Petersburg: A Visit with Stella Kerouac [bound in one volume] [1 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Horse hauling out of Hokkaido forest; Lives of the French Impressionist painters; Kerouac's Town; and St. Petersburg: A Visit with Stella Kerouac [bound in one volume] [2 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Horse hauling out of Hokkaido forest; Lives of the French Impressionist painters; Kerouac's Town; and St. Petersburg: A Visit with Stella Kerouac [bound in one volume] [3 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    TMs, 12 pp.
  - Horse hauling out of Hokkaido forest; Lives of the French Impressionist painters; Kerouac's Town; and St. Petersburg: A Visit with Stella Kerouac [bound in one volume] [4 of 4], undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [1 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [2 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [3 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [4 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [5 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    TMs, 23 pp.
  - The Horse in the Field: A Western Romance [6 of 6], undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [1 of 3], undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    "Preface", "Tricks," TMs, 25 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [2 of 3], undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    "Blackout," TMs, 19 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [3 of 3], undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    "Mrs. Kashfi," TMs, 17 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [1 of 3], undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    "Mrs. Kashfi," AMs, 13 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [2 of 3], 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    "Tricks," AMs, 26 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy [3 of 3], 1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    "Tricks," AMs, 27 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: typewritten draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    TMs, 44 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: copy of corrected galley [1 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: copy of corrected galley [2 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    TMs, pp. 51 -76
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: galley [1 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: galley [2 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: television schedule, San Jose Mercury News, featuring cover devoted to HBO series "Hotel Room", 1993 Jan 3-9 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: Tricks, a teleplay, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: Tricks, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: Tricks, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: Blackout, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    TMs with holographic notes, 21 pp.
  - The Hotel Room Trilogy: program from Pacific Film Archive of "Hotel Room" with appearance by Gifford, 1993 Mar 4 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    TMs, 2 pp.
  - Gifford's Rough Guide to these States, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    AMs, 1 pp.
  - Hotel Room Trilogy: Correspondence Between Gifford and University of Mississippi Press, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    6 TLsS, 10 TLs, 2 ALsS
  - Hotel Room Trilogy: Program for "Blackout", College of Notre Dame Production, 1994, Apr 13-16 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Room Trilogy: Reviews, advertisements, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    21 pp.
  - Hotel Room Trilogy: Reviews, Notices of HBO's "Hotel Room," Directed by David Lynch, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    1 AMs, 9 pp.
  - Hotel Room Trilogy: Cover photography by Alan Frame, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    1 photograph: b & w; 21 x 25 cm.
  - The Incredible Diving Moose: original manuscript [children's story], undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    TMs, 4 pp.
  - The Incredible Diving Moose, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    TMs, 3 pp., 1 ANS
  - Isle of Flowers: Travels in the State of Florida, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    TMs with holographic notes, 11 pp.
  - Jack's Book: New York Daily News Clipping, 1994, May 17 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Jack's Book: Correspondence From St. Martin's Press, 1994 Jul 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    1 TLS, 1 ALS, 4 pp
  - Jack's Book: Introduction to the New Edition [2 copies], undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Jack's Book: Introduction to the New Edition [galleys], undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    TMs, 7 pp.
  - Jack's Book: Introduction to the New Edition [, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Landscape with Traveler: Original Typescript [1 of 5], undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Landscape with Traveler: Original Typescript [2 of 5], undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Landscape with Traveler: Original Typescript [3 of 5], undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Landscape with Traveler: Original Typescript [4 of 5], undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    TMs, pp. iv, 1-50
  - Landscape with Traveler: Original Typescript [5 of 5], undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    TMs, pp. 50a-75
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves [1 of 4], undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    TMs, pp. 1-51
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves [2 of 4], undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    TMs, pp. 51-101
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves [3 of 4], undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    TMs, pp. 102-151
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves [4 of 4], undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    TMs, pp. 152-175
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves: [1 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
    TMsS with holographic notes, pp. 1-50
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves: [2 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 24)